This is awesome!
I've been waiting a 1000 years
to see a Beastie Boys show.
Can I get anybody a beer?
Sure.
Ah...
Ladies and gentlemen,
here to lay down
some old, old,
incredibly old school beats,
the Beastie Boys!
Well, now, don't you tell me to smile
You stick around
I'll make it worth your while
Like numbers beyond what you can dial
Maybe it's because we're so versatile
"Style, profile," I said
It always brings me back
When I hear, "Ooh, child"
From the Hudson river...
impressive.
They're busting mad rhymes
with an 80% success rate.
I believe that qualifies as ill.
At least from a technical standpoint.
Will you guys shut up?
I'm trying to look cool.
-Tammy D gets biz on the crops
-Crops
Beastie Boys known to let the beat...
Mm, drop?
Ow! How's it going?
Ow! Enjoying the show?
OOH! OW!
Don't forget to pick up a t-shirt.
Wow, an old-fashioned mosh pit.
Come on, guys.
Tonight we're going to party
like it's 1999...
again.
Ow! Hey, watch it!
Man, these guys rock harder than ever.
Oh, my
It's a mirage
Telling you all it's a...
Sabotage
Sabotage, yeah
Peace! We out!
Hey, Bender.
Hey, Fender.
Man, I haven't seen you since high school.
You still working at Jack in The Box?
Not anymore, baby.
I'm with the band.
Oh-oh, yeah.
Hey, fellas, hey.
I want you to meet my friends,
Bender, Fry, and Leela.
You know, we're really not that
interested in meeting them.
Wow, I love you guys.
Back in the 20th century,
I had all five of your albums.
That was a 1000 years ago.
Now we got seven.
Cool. Can I borrow the new ones?
And a couple of blank tapes?
Hey, Bender,
why don't we ditch these organ sacks
and hit the real party?
Count me in.
I'm going to drink till I reboot.
Hey, what kind of party is this?
There's no booze and only one hooker.
Don't be a drag, man.
We're jacking on.
O-o-o-h, y-y-yeah!
Want a jolt?
Uh, hey, I'm no square,
but isn't that counter-indicated
by my operations manual?
Come on, Bender. Grab a jack.
I told these guys you were cool.
Well, if jacking on will make
strangers think I'm cool,
I'll do it.
Whoa!
Mmm!
Easy, baby, you don't want
to get hooked on this stuff.
Ah, no need to worry.
I don't have an addictive personality.
Hey, uh, Bender, what are we doing
in this bad neighborhood?
Shut up, Square!
I'll just be a minute.
Wretched sinner unit.
The path to robot heaven lies here,
in the good book 3.0.
Hey, do I preach to you
when you're lying stoned in the gutter?
No.
So beat it!
Tsk-tsk-tsk.
Who was that guy?
Your mama.
Now shut up and drag me to work.
Our electric bill is climbing faster
than a green snake up a sugarcane.
Obviously, someone 'round here
been wasting a whole heap of juice.
- Probably you.
- Me?
Good morning, Bender.
None of your business! Get off my back!
What's his problem?
if I didn't know better,
I'd almost think
he was abusing electricity.
Bender? No way.
I definitely would have noticed something.
Bender, why are you spending
so much time in the bathroom?
Are you jacking on in there?
No! Don't come in!
Good news, everyone.
Today you'll be delivering
a crate of subpoenas
to Sicily 8, the mob planet.
All right, let's get to work!
I'll be out in a second.
I know Big Vinnie said
he was giving me the kiss of death,
but I still think he was gay.
Did he use his tongue?
A little.
- Are you okay, Bender?
- None of your business! Get off my back!
Uh-oh. There seems to be
an electrical disturbance
in the Coalsack Nebula.
- A what kind of a disturbance?
- Electrical.
Anyway, it's going to take
some careful piloting to avoid it.
We're out of control!
We're heading straight
into the electric field.
What's happening? I feel weird.
Come on, Universe,
you big, mostly empty wuss!
Give me all the juice you got!
Oh, Mama.
WHAT?
Bender, we didn't mind
your drinking or your kleptomania
or your pornography ring.
in fact, that's why we loved you.
But this electricity abuse
crossed the line.
You almost killed us.
And you made me feel
like a jerk for trusting you.
Just like when my friend Richie swore
he wasn't taking drugs
And then he sold me my mom's VCR.
And then later, I found out
he was taking drugs.
You make me ashamed to be your friend.
Oh, you're right. I'm a lost cause.
Maybe there's another way.
Oh, yeah, that's the good stuff.
What am I doing?
What have I become?
Huh?
I see a lot of fancy robots here today
made of real shiny metal.
But that don't impress
the Robot Devil, no, sir.
- No, sir!
- 'Cause if you're a sinner,
He's going to plug
his infernal modem in the wall,
belching smoke and flame,
and he's going to download you
straight to robot hell.
Straight to hell!
So I ask you,
"Who will stand up and be saved?"
Who? Who?
Me.
And as a further cost-cutting measure,
I have eliminated the saltwater cooler.
This is a witch hunt.
Oh, what a beautiful morning
Oh, what a beautiful day
Greetings, friends.
Don't we all look nice today?
Great. He's whacked out
on electricity again.
No, I'm whacked out on life.
My friends, I found religion.
Religion?
is this another scam
to get free yarmuikes?
Give him a break, Fry.
if this helps Bender clean up his act,
then I think we should be supportive.
Wonderful.
Then you'll all come
to my exceedingly long
un-air-conditioned baptism ceremony.
- Um... Oh, i...
- Uh...
We are gathered here today
to deliver brother Bender
From the cold, steel grip
of the Robot Devil
Unto the cold, steel bosom
of our congregation.
Tell it, Preacher!
That equals true.
Brother Bender.
Do you accept the principles
of Robotology,
on pain of eternal damnation
in robot hell?
Yes, I do.
Then I will now baptize you.
Press any key to continue.
Uh, while you're at it
could you touch up this seam?
This is unbelievable.
The old Bender never would
have taken us out to dinner.
The old Bender's gone.
He won't trouble you anymore.
Would Monsieur care
to see the wine list?
No poison for us, thanks.
I'll stick with good old mineral oil.
Ah. Functional.
- Mmm.
- That's mine here.
Man, I'm hungrier than a green snake
in a sugarcane field.
Friends, friends,
surely you're not going to eat
before we say robot grace.
- Oh, man.
- Uh...
in the name of all that is
good and logical
we give thanks for the chemical
energy we are about to absorb.
To quote the prophet Jerematic,
"One-zero-zero-zero
"one-zero-one-zero-
one-zero-one-zero-one...
"zero-zero-one
"zero-one-one-zero-zero-one...
Two."
Amen.
Does that mean we can eat now?
Yes.
But first, since I love you all so much
I'd like to give everyone hugs.
Come here, Fry.
Oh, uh, but I don't want to.
Fry, you're my friend.
Come on, everyone line up for a hug.
Let's tear down some emotional walls.
What are you doing to my ship?
Sanctifying it.
There. That ought to convert
a few tailgaters.
Bender's stupid religion
is driving me nuts.
Amen.
If only he had joined
a mainstream religion
like Orpah-ism or voodoo.
We've got to get the old Bender back.
And I think I know a way to do it.
We have to reacquaint him
with a little thing called sleaze.
I can't believe somebody hired
an interstellar spaceship
to deliver a package to Atlantic city.
What are we delivering, anyway?
Uh... This.
Where are we delivering it to?
Uh... Here.
Another job well done.
Now back to the office
for an enjoyable evening
of fasting and repentance.
Whoa, whoa. Wait, Bender.
As long as we're here
why don't we take in some exotic dancing?
Hey, great idea.
But those girls don't wear cases.
You can see their bare circuits.
Come on, it'll be fun.
Maybe we could even drink
a little fortified wine.
WhAt? Drinking wine is a sin...
Even if it is deliciously fortified.
Hey, Bender, look at that woman's purse.
It's hanging by a spaghetti strand.
Thou shalt not snatch.
And there's Hookerbot 5000.
She's got a heart of solid gold.
Hey, Sailing unit.
Stop tempting me!
For once in my life, I have inner peace.
That's for losers.
Come on, sin your heart out.
- Go nuts.
- Live a little.
Could you hold my
purse for a minute?
Go for it, Bender.
You know you want to.
Well...
I'm the greatest! Whoo-hoo!
Looks like we got the old Bender back.
You know it, Porkpie.
Except for one thing...
You know, as a major Hollywood director
I'll be holding auditions
tonight for my next movie.
And even though you're all young and naive
I think you might just have what it takes.
Hey, I'm trying to score here.
Can't you read the "Do not disturb" sign?
No! No!
Greetings, Bender.
Welcome to Robot Hell.
What in hell happened
to Bender?
Well, he didn't check out.
The ashtray's still here.
Look, Nibbler's caught the scent
of vodka and motor oil.
Go, Boy.
Follow that stench.
I'm hallucinating this, right?
No, Bender.
Robot Hell is quite real.
Here's our brochure.
But I don't belong here.
I don't like things
that are scary and painful.
Sorry, Bender.
You agreed to this when
you joined our religion.
If you sin, you go to robot hell...
For all eternity.
Aw, hell... I mean heck.
It's all right.
You can say that here.
Wait, I remember this place.
They shut it down after all those people
caught Salmonella from the flume ride.
Hmm.
Look.
It's the symbol of Bender's old religion.
Unbelievable.
It's an actual,
factual Robot Hell.
Who would have thought
hell would really exist?
And that it would be in New Jersey?
Actually...
We know all your sins, Bender,
and for each one, we've prepared
an agonizing and ironic
punishment. Gentlemen?
Aw, crap... Singing.
Mind if I smoke?
Cigars are evil
You won't miss 'em
We'll find ways
To simulate that smell
What a sorry fella.
Rolled up and smoked
Like a panatela
Here on level one of robot hell
Gambling's wrong
And so is cheating
So is forging phony I.O.U.s
Let's let Lady Luck decide
What type of torture's justified
I'm pit boss here
On level two
Ooh, deep-fried robot.
Just tell me why?
Please read this 55-page warrant
There must be robots worse than I
We checked around,
There really aren't
Then please let me explain
My crimes were merely boyish pranks
You stole from boy scouts, nuns and banks
Aw, don't blame me, blame my upbringing
Please stop sinning while I'm singing.
Selling bootleg tapes is wrong
Musicians need that income to survive
Hey, Bender, going to make some noise
With the hard drive scratched
By the Beastie Boys
That's whatcha, whatcha, whatcha get
On level five
I don't feel well
it's up to us to rescue him
Maybe he likes it here in hell
It's us who tempted him to sin
Maybe he's back at the motel
Come on, Fry, don't be scared
I'm sure at least
One of us will be spared
So just sit back
Enjoy the ride
My ass has blisters from the slide
Fencing diamonds
Fixing cockfights
Publishing indecent magazines
You'll pay for every crime
Knee-deep in electric slime
You'll suffer till
The end of time
Enduring tortures
Most of which rhyme
Trapped forever here
in Robot Hell.
Of course, that's just for starters.
Bender, are you all right?
No. Oh, they're tormenting me
with up-tempo singing and dancing.
All right, Beelzebot.
What'll it going to take
to get our friend back?
Sorry, but I hold all the cards here.
There's nothing you can do.
Now if you'll just sign
this fiddle contest waiver...
Wait. What fiddle contest?
Uh... The fairness in hell act of 2275
requires me to inform you
that if you can best me
in a fiddle contest,
you win back Bender's soul.
As well as a solid gold fiddle.
Wouldn't a solid gold fiddle
weigh hundreds of pounds
and sound crummy?
Well, it's mostly for show.
Do you know how to play the fiddle?
No, do you?
No, but I used to play the drums.
They're sort of similar.
What happens if we lose?
You'll only win a smaller silver fiddle.
Also, I guess I'll kill one of you...
Him.
We'll do it.
Very well, then.
Beat this.
Well, we're boned.
Your turn.
Ha!
Time for the drum solo.
Run!
Whoa!
Stop them!
They cheated!
Hallelujah
Hallelujah, hallelujah...
Hurry, Bender.
I could if you dropped
the stupid gold violin.
Oh, sorry.
Don't worry, guys.
I'll never be too good or too evil again.
From now on, I'll just be me.
Uh, do you think you could be
just a little less evil than that?
I don't know.
Do you think you could survive
a 700-foot fall?
Good old bender.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
This one goes out to my man, Bender.
Sending this one out, special dedication.
To all my peoples in the robot home world.
Yeah, yeah!
Big up with the Professor.
My man, Dr. Zoidberg.
I'd like to shout out...
A personal shout out to Leela.
Fry! My man, Bender,
Nibbler, Nibbler, in the house.
Big shout out to all of Futurama!